{
    "id": "15bdb9f97e26444592da5dc994df6169",
    "title": "Conjunctions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He worked hard ……………………….. he might get the first rank.",
            "description": "We use so that to express purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "provided that",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you pay for your food, you can stay with me.",
            "description": "As long as is used to express a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "As long as",
                "As far as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was late and ………………………… were the others.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "thus"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke in ………………………….. a low voice that we could not hear anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you ……………………….. I reach home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "soon",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We waited …………………………. they came.",
            "description": "Until shows time. ",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I usually get up early ………………………… today I got up late.",
            "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. he was angry, I said nothing.",
            "description": "Because is used to express the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "So",
                "Hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is one of the few politicians …………………………. I admire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "whom",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he apologizes we will not take any further action against him.",
            "description": "If is used to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I had a headache, I enjoyed the film.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ……………………… I live is quite large.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}